[{"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5ce", "question": "What are the names of the Pep Boys?", "answer": "Manny, Moe, and Jack", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339616", "question": "Alfred Hitchcock's 1948 film \"Rope\" was based on a real-life crime committed by who?", "answer": "Leopold & Loeb", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdd9", "question": "What name is given to the full moon closest to the autumn equinox?", "answer": "Harvest moon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389d9", "question": "What book does each girl receive as a Christmas present at the start of \"Little Women\"?", "answer": "The Pilgrim's Progress", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0b6", "question": "Maraschino is a liqueur made from what fruit?", "answer": "Marasca cherries", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5be581145415ba52ed6f0abd", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"The History of Mr Polly\"?", "answer": "H. G. Wells", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396c3", "question": "How many teeth does Bugs Bunny have?", "answer": "Two", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59675c4d2b59efe0e9417e94", "question": "What was Vince Gill\u2019s last #1 as a solo recording artist?", "answer": "Tryin\u2019 To Get over You", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fae", "question": "What nickname is shared by Charles Russell, Harold Reese, and Paul Reubens?", "answer": "Pee-Wee", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fefc1676ce05a3942286f11", "question": "Which famous Swedish DJ's name meams the part of hell where the baddest sinners go to?", "answer": "Avicii", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1df", "question": "In the restaurant world, what does \"Blue-plate special\" refer to?", "answer": "Low-priced specials that change daily", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bff8", "question": "Bibliophobia is a fear or hatred of what?", "answer": "Books", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe9f07aff048f679a45aa9d", "question": "Pteromerhanophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Flying", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe0e386fcbed638185eaa22", "question": "What U.S. state is nicknamed \"The Sooner State\"?", "answer": "Oklahoma", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58ec22f68dc25ca9e12ef62b", "question": "As whom was J\u00e1n Ludv\u00edk Hyman Binyamin Hoch better known?", "answer": "Robert Maxwell", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133969a", "question": "The 1975 movie \"The Man Who Would Be King\" is based on the tales of which author?", "answer": "Rudyard Kipling", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a52", "question": "What TV family had three sons named Brad, Mark, and Randy?", "answer": "The Taylor's from Home Improvement", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf76", "question": "What is the fear of getting wrinkles known as?", "answer": "Rhytiphobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ae4", "question": "What 2001 Rachael Leigh Cook film was based on an old Saturday morning cartoon series?", "answer": "Josie and the Pussycats", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a93", "question": "What song appears on the \"Saturday Night Fever\" soundtrack twice, once by the Bee Gees and once by Tavares?", "answer": "More Than a Woman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58ab1832baab681b09292187", "question": "Which racing team introduced a six-wheeled race car in 1974 and began racing it in 1976?", "answer": "Tyrrell Racing", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8b3", "question": "What is the main ingredient of guacamole?", "answer": "Avocados", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abc2", "question": "What country borders Albania to the south?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b18", "question": "What is Mozart's full name?", "answer": "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395a7", "question": "In what fictitious town does \"Invasion of the Body Snatchers\" take place?", "answer": "Hicksville, USA", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb34", "question": "In the late 1990\u2019s, what candy bar used the ad slogan \"Two for me, none for you\"?", "answer": "Twix", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe775edeec85e375820b313", "question": "How many states does Mexico have?", "answer": "31", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f5b", "question": "What artist sang the 1972 number 1 US hit, \"Alone Again (Naturally)\"?", "answer": "Gilbert O'Sulivan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c20a", "question": "Which country was selected as a host of the 1916 Olympic Games, but didn't actually host them?", "answer": "Germany", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac99", "question": "Which of the US Presidents was the first to be born in the 20th century?", "answer": "Lyndon B. Johnson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5bfdffe3b668d7dfe168b5bd", "question": "Chablis wine comes from which French wine region?", "answer": "Burgundy", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59f9bbef364247bf200fb8ab", "question": "What country borders Zambia to the east?", "answer": "Malawi", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133beea", "question": "Electric, Perse and smalt are shades of which color?", "answer": "Blue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c658", "question": "Mach refers to the speed of what?", "answer": "Sound", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe7d079877e98cb97778a62", "question": "In which US state can you find the \"Garden of the Gods\"?", "answer": "Colorado", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a85b", "question": "On which harbour is the Sydney Opera House located?", "answer": "Sydney Harbour", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb0f", "question": "In what country is Guinness Stout brewed?", "answer": "Ireland", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6e2", "question": "What is the fastest animal on earth that runs on two legs?", "answer": "The ostrich", "category": "science"}, {"id": "600394d257a0e35c43f8388e", "question": "What painting technique was employed by Ribera, and other painters, in order to focus a spotlight on certain areas of a painting?", "answer": "Tenebrism", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a979", "question": "What nation's legislative body is named The Eduskunta?", "answer": "Finland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339490", "question": "Anthony Hopkins played a ventriloquist in which 1978 movie?", "answer": "Magic", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58ab189bbaab681b0929218c", "question": "What country is home to Volvo?", "answer": "Sweden", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abd3", "question": "Hamilton is the capital of which British Overseas Territory?", "answer": "Bermuda", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b42e", "question": "How old was Alfred Hitchcock when he died?", "answer": "80", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a9e92d97ccba3ffe45786bd", "question": "Who wrote the 1932 comic novel \"Cold Comfort Farm\"?", "answer": "Stella Gibbons", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e91", "question": "What detective novel begins with a dinner hosted by the mysteriously absent \"Mr. U. N. Owen\"?", "answer": "And Then There Were None", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0c3", "question": "What would be scored by the Apgar score?", "answer": "Health of newborns", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6a5", "question": "In the game of poker, who was the hand referred to as \"dead man's hand\" named after?", "answer": "Wild Bill Hickok", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b69930be762b54eb9be9428", "question": "In which US state would you find Twenty Lake?", "answer": "Minnesota", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac5b", "question": "What year did the Bhopal disaster occur?", "answer": "1984", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58c8a83b90aac110e416708c", "question": "Who said \"He that drinks his cider alone, let him catch his horse alone.\"?", "answer": "Benjamin Franklin", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ea3", "question": "What youngest brother of the music world was a former host of \"Solid Gold\"?", "answer": "Andy Gibb", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59ca3e3b44f0f6af5b066648", "question": "In mathematics, which prefix refers to 10 to the power of minus 24?", "answer": "Yocto", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a212", "question": "What was the name of the dog in the TV series \"Fraggle Rock\"?", "answer": "Sprocket", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b27", "question": "What 1991 River Phoenix/Keanu Reeves film took its title from lyrics in a B-52's song?", "answer": "My Own Private Idaho", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0b091e662d71a53650fca", "question": "What part of New York did Vito Corleone grow up in?", "answer": "After Vito flees Sicily, he finds shelter with the Abbandando family in Little Italy, New York.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffa52a7c73aa70ea0b70b1c", "question": "Frankenmuth, a U.S. city nicknamed \"Little Bavaria\", is located in what state?", "answer": "Michigan (It is a German-style town in Saginaw County. It is well known for its hotels and old-style German buildings.)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339329", "question": "In \"The Godfather\", who plays Michael Corleone?", "answer": "Al Pacino", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58ab1ad1baab681b09292197", "question": "Which car is considered to be the first hot hatchback, introduced in the 1970s?", "answer": "The Simca 1100 TI", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7c934877e98cb977789f1", "question": "What is Africa's oldest continuous democracy?", "answer": "Botswana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "60121ae563c99d48cd169b09", "question": "An \"octothorpe\" refers to which popular social media symbol?", "answer": "Hashtag -- It is also called the \"pound sign\".", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c60", "question": "George Lucas' first full feature film, \"THX 1138\" was released in what year?", "answer": "1971", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58b8d58d2b42d4a3561a9f03", "question": "In the comic book series \"Strangers in Paradise\", what brand of condoms is Francine selected to represent on the first day of her new job?", "answer": "Command Purpose Condoms", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6014c8d4fbde8045e48466e1", "question": "Why do some plants send chemical signals to bugs?", "answer": "Signal for help -- Leafy tobacco plants send a chemical signal to wasps, who will seek out caterpillars eating the leaves.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe733f0eec85e375820b229", "question": "What naval battle between Mark Antony and Octavian is often said to mark the beginning of the Roman Empire?", "answer": "Battle of Actium", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388fa", "question": "Who created Hercule Poirot and Miss Marple?", "answer": "Agatha Christie", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339308", "question": "In the 1987 movie \"Fatal Attraction\", what animal did the obsessed woman cook on the stove?", "answer": "A rabbit", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390f2", "question": "Who is typically referred to as \"The Father of History\"?", "answer": "Herodotus", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff2588c31a458464a93c467", "question": "What does the Slavic word \"vodka\" translate to in English?", "answer": "\"Little water\"", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a4a957561d1b4d384d5d67a", "question": "Who, or what, was the \"First Reich\"?", "answer": "The Holy Roman Empire", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b592", "question": "What does the abbreviation SUV stand for?", "answer": "Sport Utility Vehicle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5feba99a7e83c707845b20d7", "question": "What is the name given to the white part of a person's eye?", "answer": "Sclera", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ff", "question": "Who painted the Mona Lisa?", "answer": "Leonardo da Vinci", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "594a644f2ebb971c1417fba3", "question": "Who was the first person to swim across Lake Ontario?", "answer": "Marilyn Bell", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad12", "question": "Who was the first Western European Emperor since the collapse of the Western Roman Empire?", "answer": "Charlemagne", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6012125263c99d48cd169ae1", "question": "\"Prehistory\" refers to the era before what?", "answer": "Writing -- The Prehistoric Era lasted from around 12,000 to 3,000 B.C.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bca4", "question": "What is the heating element in Hasbro's Easy-Bake Oven\"?", "answer": "A lightbulb", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c91", "question": "What John Steinbeck novel is based on the biblical story of Cain & Abel?", "answer": "East of Eden", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d3f", "question": "In Italian, the Mona Lisa is called what?", "answer": "La Giocondo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59049ca0cf93664eb10486a8", "question": "Which famous rapper died on Friday, September 13, 1996?", "answer": "Tupac Shakur", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1cc", "question": "Whose execution caused the famed Spanish Armada to sail against England?", "answer": "Mary, Queen of Scots'", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5feccd95ec223966ae8f88ac", "question": "In \"Deadpool\", Wade Wilson teams up with Colossus and what other member of the X-men?", "answer": "Negasonic Teenage Warhead", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339155", "question": "What is a platinum record awarded for?", "answer": "An LP selling a million copies", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea80c8ff048f679a45ac1c", "question": "The Black Death was caused by fleas carried by what animal?", "answer": "Rodents", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3ae", "question": "What name was given to textile workers who opposed modernisation during the 19th century?\u00a0", "answer": "Luddites\u00a0", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ba3", "question": "Who wrote the play, \"A Streetcar Named Desire\"?", "answer": "Tennessee Williams", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392d2", "question": "What was Murray Langston better known as to the public?", "answer": "The Unknown Comic", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397f8", "question": "Which group had albums called \"Fireball\" and \"Machine Head\"?", "answer": "Deep Purple", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59a1a1e512f2a7826b9b8716", "question": "What was the name given to the French goverment which collaborated with the Nazis?", "answer": "Vichy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb9a", "question": "In what year did the Pillsbury doughboy first appear on TV?", "answer": "1965", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fde494bc6c6b019850c9a6e", "question": "What was the first Christian country in Africa?", "answer": "Ethiopia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca8d", "question": "In what year was nylon first synthesized?", "answer": "1935", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b675", "question": "What was William Fox Talbot a pioneer of?", "answer": "Photography", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c004", "question": "What is philately the study of?", "answer": "Stamps", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c91d", "question": "Which part of the body does the adjective \"renal\" refer to?", "answer": "Kidney", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5b7abb606490a8cc1a6e5296", "question": "How many flavors of quarks are there?", "answer": "6", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe69dce20565ad31a57c77d", "question": "Where did the concept of \"rolling out the red carpet\" originate?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc50", "question": "Which University did Lady Gaga attend before dropping out to pursue her music career?", "answer": "New York University", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9bd", "question": "Which country's days include Fire day, Water day and Wood day?", "answer": "Japan's", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b49e", "question": "Which country hosted the first Olympic Games after World War I?", "answer": "Belgium", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58dba5e4874c93a3298b2154", "question": "What is formed when light is bent by layers of hot air?", "answer": "A mirage", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d0c", "question": "What historical event provides the backdrop for the 1905 novel \"The Scarlet Pimpernel\"?", "answer": "The French Revolution", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7c4", "question": "Who won a Nobel Prize for discovering Penicillin?", "answer": "Alexander Fleming", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ddb", "question": "Why was paradise paved over, according to Joni Mitchell's \"Big Yellow Taxi\"?", "answer": "To put up a parking lot", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd82445d0de9af39e9d46b9", "question": "Which U.S. president spoke English as a second language?", "answer": "Martin Van Buren", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea40caff048f679a45ab6a", "question": "What word is the definition of 100,000 BTUs?", "answer": "One therm", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aedf", "question": "Which missionary and saint founded a monastery on the island of Iona?", "answer": "St. Columba", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c80b", "question": "Which of the four bases of DNA isn't found in RNA?", "answer": "Thymine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ad7eb8eb24f84e0b9f9ffde", "question": "What state borders Alabama to the north?", "answer": "Tennessee", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c929", "question": "What is a bactrian?", "answer": "Two-humped camel", "category": "science"}, {"id": "600244cb4be4723ccac221a8", "question": "What painting attracted more visitors to the Louvre Museum after it was stolen?", "answer": "When the\u00a0\"Mona Lisa\"\u00a0was stolen in 1911, it caused a media sensation, and visitors queued for hours to see the vacant wall.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a1", "question": "Who is known as Slim Shady?", "answer": "Marshall Mathers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2df", "question": "How many pounds of honey is eaten by bees to produce 1 pound of beeswax?", "answer": "8 Pounds", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d0b", "question": "What woman's rise to fame is the subject of the 1997 book \"Just Desserts\"?", "answer": "Martha Stewart", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e08", "question": "What does Doctor Who's vast spacecraft, the TARDIS, look like from the outside?", "answer": "A police box", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c227", "question": "Who claims to have invented the Mai Tai cocktail in 1944?", "answer": "Victor J. Bergeron", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fef5f306ce05a3942286e3f", "question": "Who died tragically young outside L.A.'s Viper Room club?", "answer": "River Phoenix", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa2d", "question": "What's the capital of Comoros?", "answer": "Moroni", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe76838eec85e375820b29d", "question": "What group of countries are often referred to as Great Britain?", "answer": "England, Scotland, and Wales", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea48f2ff048f679a45abb5", "question": "Pes planus refers to which condition?", "answer": "Flat feet", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ade1", "question": "What year did the Han Dynasty come into power?", "answer": "206 BC", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6a6d120565ad31a57c7df", "question": "Who was the first U.S. Postmaster General?", "answer": "Benjamin Franklin", "category": "history"}, {"id": "600b883a1d8c1817608d53ef", "question": "Which popular Mexican dish consists of chopped meat in a stew with red chillies and kidney beans?", "answer": "Chilli con carne", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc83", "question": "What Asian country bans the importation and sale of chewing gum?", "answer": "Singapore", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb7c", "question": "What brand of breakfast cereal has the phrase \"Two Scoops!\" emblazoned on its box?", "answer": "Kellogg's Raisin Bran", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe64163ae7e414034b5aeac", "question": "What was the name of Al Capone's criminal organization?", "answer": "The Outfit", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133940c", "question": "Who played Uncle Buck in the movie \"Uncle Buck\"?", "answer": "John Candy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394cd", "question": "What variety show host fired Julius LaRosa live, on the air?", "answer": "Arthur Godfrey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58c9f811b4e2c7fbd389674f", "question": "What country does Cafe au lait originate from?", "answer": "France", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af7d", "question": "What constitutional amendment established prohibition in the US?", "answer": "18th Constitutional Amendment", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff670f552a821ff76ae8b23", "question": "Who invented \"Jell-O\"?", "answer": "Pearle Wait", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a594", "question": "What is the smallest ocean?", "answer": "The Arctic Ocean", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c182", "question": "What is the name for the number 1 followed by 100 zeros?", "answer": "Googol", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa77", "question": "What is the capital of Malawi?", "answer": "Lilongwe", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "60173c3444491cbd7c5a17a4", "question": "What collectively-named languages evolved from Vulgar Latin?", "answer": "Romance or romanic language -- The five most spoken romance languages are Spanish, French, Portuguese, Italian and Romanian.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd35", "question": "What sports term is the shortest word ever to decide the National Spelling Bee?", "answer": "Luge", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c60b", "question": "What is the fear of washing or bathing called?", "answer": "Ablutophobia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133959f", "question": "What is Ace Ventura's occupation in the movies by the same name?", "answer": "Pet detective", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a220", "question": "Which tough guy actor was once a linotype operator?", "answer": "Robert Mitchum", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdabec80b8cce1e6fda7066", "question": "What is the main ingredient in the Malaysian dish called Nasi Lemak?", "answer": "Rice", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133944b", "question": "In what Arizona city does the movie \"Psycho\" begin?", "answer": "Phoenix", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133921a", "question": "What female singer is discussed at the start of the movie \"Reservoir Dogs\"?", "answer": "Madonna", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffa550dc73aa70ea0b70b20", "question": "Hastings, England has a distinct May Day festival which is known as what?", "answer": "Jack in the Green", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1bb", "question": "At the 1996 Olympics, what American tied Mark Spitz's lifetime record of nine golds?", "answer": "Carl Lewis", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398e6", "question": "What was the name of the 90's TV show starring Jamie Lee Curtis and comedian Richard Lewis?", "answer": "Anything But Love", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5c77ce1c24f0f7a362efd544", "question": "Who sang \"It's my party and I'll cry if I want to...\"?", "answer": "Lesley Gore", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caea", "question": "What invention is Arthur W. Savage often linked with?", "answer": "The radial tire", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fede1246ce05a3942286dc2", "question": "Where is Graceland, the legendary home of Elvis Presley?", "answer": "Memphis, Tennessee", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9fe", "question": "Hawaii's Kalaupapa was known as a refuge for those suffering from what disease?", "answer": "Leprosy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4de", "question": "What is the largest lake in Central America?", "answer": "Lake Nicaragua", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397f5", "question": "Who wrote the song \"Mr Tambourine Man\"?", "answer": "Bob Dylan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7c88b877e98cb977789e8", "question": "Where can you drive the Road to Hana?", "answer": "Maui, Hawaii", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea366cff048f679a45ab0d", "question": "What are the bones in the fingers called?", "answer": "Phalanges", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd2f", "question": "What original animal mascot for Trix cereal was replaced by a rabbit in 1967?", "answer": "Flamingo", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ae85fc14007905755f79e8c", "question": "What is the largest river delta in the world?", "answer": "The Ganges-Brahmaputra Delta", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6e6", "question": "What two states share a border with Florida?", "answer": "Alabama and Georgia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fec845aec223966ae8f87fe", "question": "Which Mario character has appeared in all but one \"Mario Party\" game?", "answer": "Wario", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aadb", "question": "What is the capital of Croatia?\u00a0", "answer": "Zagreb\u00a0", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6017404244491cbd7c5a17bd", "question": "What was Vladimir Lenin's birth name?", "answer": "Vladimir Ilyich Ulyanov -- \"Lenin\" was an alias.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5ef", "question": "How many red stripes are there on the American flag?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe6a25720565ad31a57c7ab", "question": "Which brewery won the \"top beer award\" at Chicago's World Fair in 1893?", "answer": "Pabst Brewing Company", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a513", "question": "In which sea is the island country of Malta?", "answer": "Mediterranean", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5a162b32f01ec323f8491727", "question": "What is the name of Natalie Merchant's debut solo album after leaving 10000 Maniacs?", "answer": "Tigerlily", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea3d77ff048f679a45ab4e", "question": "A unit of measure of absorbed radiation is known as what?", "answer": "Rad", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8f6", "question": "What units are ship speeds measured in?", "answer": "Knots", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe7bf10877e98cb97778965", "question": "What is the smallest country in South America?", "answer": "Suriname", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7e6", "question": "In what city is Gonzaga University located?", "answer": "Spokane, Washington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cb7", "question": "What TV show featured the fictional \"The Cobra Lodge\" fraternity?", "answer": "Mama's Family", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1f2", "question": "What was the last country in the Americas to abolish slavery, in 1888?", "answer": "Brazil", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133918e", "question": "Who is smarter than the average bear?", "answer": "Yogi Bear", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "590720743745b36be73039f1", "question": "What do all the victims in the 1984 film \"Don\u2019t Open Till Christmas\" all have in common?", "answer": "They were wearing Santa Claus suits or items of clothing", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c996", "question": "Heroin is the brand name of morphine once marketed by which pharmaceutical company?", "answer": "Bayer", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391fb", "question": "Who played Vincent Vega in \"Pulp Fiction\"?", "answer": "John Travolta", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59ded148ea2747c8aff16d31", "question": "What Hebrew word means \"so be it\"?", "answer": "Amen", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2e9", "question": "What group's 1979 debut album was entitled \"Reproduction\"?", "answer": "Human League", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ca5", "question": "Who wrote the science-fiction novel \"The Time Machine\"?", "answer": "H. G. Wells", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398f6", "question": "What Beatles song begins with the opening fanfare from the French national anthem?", "answer": "All You Need is Love", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe76a00eec85e375820b2b7", "question": "In what modern day country did the seven Churches of Asia once exist?", "answer": "Turkey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b857", "question": "What number is represented in Morse code by 5 dots?", "answer": "5", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339868", "question": "In Disney's \"Dumbo\", what kind of animal is Dumbos only friend?", "answer": "A Mouse", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338957", "question": "What is by far the most famous painting in the Louvre?", "answer": "The Mona Lisa", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339aa3", "question": "What TV family had a road manager named Reuben Kincaid?", "answer": "The Partridge Family", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaec", "question": "What is the capital of Tanzania?", "answer": "Dodoma", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afb4", "question": "What was first presented at Hollywood\u2019s Roosevelt Hotel on May 16, 1929?", "answer": "The Academy Awards (Oscars)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58ab966a86faa38a764be51e", "question": "Which automotive company introduced the Phaeton in 2002?", "answer": "Volkswagen", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338cfc", "question": "Who wrote \"Memoirs of a Geisha\"?", "answer": "Arthur Golden", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c43c", "question": "What plastic often has its name shortened to PS?", "answer": "Polystyrene", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58ab1a55baab681b09292193", "question": "Which Maserati vehicle was designed and built on the Enzo Ferrari chassis?", "answer": "The MC12", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c372", "question": "How many carats is pure gold?", "answer": "24", "category": "science"}, {"id": "591c3813815febcc896f9279", "question": "What is the eigth sign of the Zodiac?", "answer": "Scorpio", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7c1cc877e98cb9777897d", "question": "What does Salzburg translate to?", "answer": "Salt Castle", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "592eb087f83302ff91e4649d", "question": "What year did filming of the 1972 film \"The Godfather\" begin?", "answer": "1971", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa1d", "question": "Jefferson City is the capital of which US state?", "answer": "Missouri", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b683", "question": "What is dentophobia a common fear of?", "answer": "Dentists", "category": "general"}, {"id": "60078bab0eee65b76b9f266b", "question": "For what is Matthew Webb famous?", "answer": "He was the first man to swim the English Channel.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b93c", "question": "Who did Charles Barkley name as \"the one player I'll accept losing to, if I have to lose\"?", "answer": "Michael Jordan", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133975f", "question": "What two murderesses does Billy Flynn represent in Chicago?", "answer": "Velma Kelly and Roxie Hart", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600245024be4723ccac221ab", "question": "In Leonardo da Vinci's Annunciation, who is depicted with the virgin Mary?", "answer": "Gabriel -- The angel is sent by God to tell the virgin Mary that she will miraculously conceive and give birth to a son, Jesus.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339176", "question": "Which Seinfeld creator plays himself in the TV show \"Curb Your Enthusiasm\"?", "answer": "Larry David", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b707", "question": "What song contains the line \"Somebody waits for you, kiss her once for me\"?", "answer": "A Holly Jolly Christmas", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393a2", "question": "Who plays Jullia Robert's best friend in the movie \"My Best Friend's Wedding\"?", "answer": "Dermot Mulroney", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0b7cfe662d71a53651018", "question": "In which city is the Prado Art Gallery?", "answer": "Madrid", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fede3946ce05a3942286dd4", "question": "Robert De Niro auditioned for which character in the film \"The Godfather\"?", "answer": "Sonny", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba95", "question": "Who was the first football coach to win both a Rose Bowl in 1976 and a Super Bowl in 2000?", "answer": "Dick Vermeil", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c21e", "question": "Who was Randy Mario Poffo better known as?", "answer": "\"Macho Man\" Randy Savage", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dc8", "question": "What double-word song title was a hit single by The Castaways?", "answer": "Liar Liar", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5b4", "question": "What planet has the shortest day, at 10 hours?", "answer": "Jupiter", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339744", "question": "What album earned the Dixie Chicks a Grammy Award in 2007?", "answer": "Taking the Long Way", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c948", "question": "What does a Geophage do?", "answer": "Eats earthy substances", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6015f6f7fe83fe1f2a824c1f", "question": "After Jesus fasted in the desert, what was His first temptation in the wilderness?", "answer": "Turn stone into bread", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1b0", "question": "Who beat Martina Navratilova in the Wimbledon Women's Singles final in 1994?", "answer": "Conchita Martinez", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fdc0f42469bb8041d07a066", "question": "Which animal was part of the Gloria Vanderbilt jeans logo?", "answer": "Swan", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7c92d877e98cb977789f0", "question": "What European city hosts an annual wine-throwing festival?", "answer": "Haro, Spain", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "590680bdff9c0647b50a808e", "question": "Which character did Anton Yelchin portray in the Star Trek film series reboot, prior to his death in 2016?", "answer": "Pavel Chekov", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58b372861c3f17ccc40c8e25", "question": "The Moho is an extinct genus of birds that were endemic to which island archipelago?", "answer": "Hawaiian Islands", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ffb67ef5dad637d903c8840", "question": "Kersti Kaljulaid was 46 years old when she became the youngest president ever elected to lead which country?", "answer": "Estonia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5e6", "question": "Which company holds the ticker symbol \"FUN\" on the New York Stock Exchange?", "answer": "Cedar Point", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398d0", "question": "Who won an Oscar for his role in the movie \"Ray\"?", "answer": "Jamie Foxx", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b357", "question": "Albert DeSalvo is better known as whom?", "answer": "The Boston Strangler", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b64a", "question": "What type of clam chowder is made with a tomato-based sauce?", "answer": "Manhattan clam chowder", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339939", "question": "What legendary record label was founded by Sam Phillips in 1952?", "answer": "Sun Records", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015fcbffe83fe1f2a824c44", "question": "The founder of Atari also founded which pizza restaurant?", "answer": "Chuck E. Cheese", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ad9dc69e748bb36357acddd", "question": "What 21st-century US presidential candidate had a spouse who was president of two colleges?", "answer": "Bernie Sanders", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6e7", "question": "What is the more common name for the bone called the furcula, found in birds?", "answer": "Wishbone", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5e90fd7fd7247dfc0fa00307", "question": "Who is the first Prime Minister of Italy, also a leading figure in the Italian unification?", "answer": "Camillo Benso", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b118", "question": "In ancient Japan, all people who gave massages had to be what?", "answer": "Blind", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac41", "question": "What was The City of Gold sought by Spanish explorers?", "answer": "El Dorado", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b037", "question": "What Major League Baseball park was originally called Weeghman Park?", "answer": "Wrigley Field", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391c2", "question": "What is Marilyn Monroe's real name?", "answer": "Norma Jeane Mortenson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c37c", "question": "Who developed the classification we use for clouds?", "answer": "Luke Howard", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c44a", "question": "How many chromosomes does a donkey have?", "answer": "62", "category": "science"}, {"id": "597cdaaae347d002c297e4d6", "question": "What nationality is Yehudi Menuhin?", "answer": "American", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59774321284458f1d7854425", "question": "Albert Einstein was offered the position of prime minister of what country?", "answer": "Israel", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b185", "question": "Who succeeded Ronald Reagan as the 41st President of the United States?", "answer": "George H.W. Bush", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c15b", "question": "What does the word Karaoke literally translate to?", "answer": "Empty Orchestra", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395e3", "question": "In The Simpsons, what was Maggie's first word?", "answer": "Daddy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0c6", "question": "What hurricane devastated Charleston, South Carolina in 1989?", "answer": "Hugo", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f6b", "question": "What is a series containing seven instalments called?", "answer": "A Heptalogy", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2d3", "question": "What is permanently-frozen subsoil called?", "answer": "Permafrost", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb97", "question": "What type of building or facility gets its name from the Greek meaning \"to exercise naked\"?", "answer": "Gymnasium", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff0b8fee662d71a5365102b", "question": "Which character opens the novel \"The Great Gatsby\"?", "answer": "Nick Carraway", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe3ee068b5801b8f54a7fb6", "question": "The ancient Romans used the word \"mala\" to refer to what food?", "answer": "Apples", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe69e1920565ad31a57c77f", "question": "What country was the first to introduce license plates?", "answer": "France", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133914a", "question": "Who wrote the 1975 novel \"Shogun\"?", "answer": "James Clavell", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1b4", "question": "Canadian Prime Minister Lester Pearson won the Nobel Peace Prize for defusing what world crisis?", "answer": "The Suez Crisis", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dcc", "question": "What double-word song title was a hit single by The Beau Brummels?", "answer": "Laugh Laugh", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2e0", "question": "What year did actor Arthur Stanley Jefferson die?", "answer": "1965", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febaeee7e83c707845b20f9", "question": "What gives eyes their color?", "answer": "Melanin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339221", "question": "Which two artists formed the band \"Wham!\"?", "answer": "George Michael and Andrew Ridgeley", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6a16920565ad31a57c7a3", "question": "Who was president when the White House got its first computer?", "answer": "Jimmy Carter", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5f164952f9b80650dbe7f92a", "question": "What is Harry Potter's middle name?", "answer": "James", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5bb35ac72627b8fe95581be9", "question": "In what country was Mel Gibson born?", "answer": "United States", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b47b", "question": "When did the Battle of the Plains of Abraham take place?", "answer": "1759", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4ed", "question": "What process does milk undergo to become yogurt?", "answer": "Bacterial fermentation", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339422", "question": "Who played the role of Jade in the 2009 movie \"The Hangover\"?", "answer": "Heather Graham", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe9f6dcff048f679a45aadf", "question": "What is Johannes Kepler best known for?", "answer": "Kepler's laws of planetary motion", "category": "science"}]